// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "With Digital Notarisation the client appears before the Notary Public via a video conference call ?",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which traditional Notary tools are converted to digital tools?",
    answer: "Wet Ink Signature, Notary Stamp, Notary Seal and Notary office",
    options: [
      "Notary Stamp, Wet Ink signature, Notary seal and Customer ID",
      "Wet Ink Signature, Notary Stamp, Notary Seal and Notary office",
      "Computer system, Notary stamp, Notary Seal and Wet Ink signature",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In the correct order what are the 5 steps to complete a Virtual Notary session?",
    answer: "Prepare for Notary call, Introduction, Confirmation of Clients, Affix your Notary Stamp/Seal, Closing",
    options: [
      "Prepare for Notary call, Introduction, Confirmation of Clients, Affix your Notary Stamp/Seal, Closing",
      "Introduction, Prepare for Notary Call, Perform, Confirmation of Clients, Closing",
      "Perform, Prepare, Confirmation of Clients, Affix your Notary Stamp/Seal",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What tools are essential to host a digital notarisation session?",
    answer: "Accessible Internet and a Laptop",
    options: [
      "Accessible Internet and a Laptop",
      "Background light and a desk",
      "A well designed Office",
      "Camera"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is a Digital Transaction Certificate?",
    answer: "A Digital Certificate is an encrypted certificate that protect files and notarised documents from being duplicated.",
    options: [
      "A Digital Certificate is an encrypted certificate that protect files and notarised documents from being duplicated.",
      "A Digital Certificate is a certificate hosted online.",
      "A Digital Certificate is a paperless certificate",
      "A Digital Certificate is an online file"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What Security Feature is NOT on the ToNote Platform?",
    answer: "Facial/Finger Print Recognition",
    options: [
      "KYC Feature",
      "Digital Cerificate",
      "Facial/Finger Print Recognition",
      "Two-factor authentification",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What do you do if a customer does not give permission for a session to be recorded?",
    answer: "Educate the client on the necessity of this step being taken",
    options: [
      "Immediately terminate the Virtual Notarisation Session",
      "Educate the client on the necessity of this step being taken",
      "Proceed to Notarise the documents uploaded for Notarisation",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A photocopy of clients means of Identification is an acceptable form of Identification on the ToNote platform?",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the first thing you need to do once you are on a Notary session call?",
    answer: "Welcome your clients and introduce yourself properly",
    options: [
      "Confirm Client Identity on the Call",
      "Welcome your clients and introduce yourself properly",
      "Go ahead and notarise the documents uploaded for the session",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How do you conclude a Notary session Call?",
    answer: "Ending the Notary session by saying 'Your Notarisation session is complete, Thank you for using ToNote'",
    options: [
      "Immediately Terminate the call once Notarisation is complete",
      "Ending the Notary session by saying 'Your Notarisation session is complete, Thank you for using ToNote'",
      "Request for clients means of identification to end the virtual session",
    ]
  },

  

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];